A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Working Papers of the Vice President, Series 18 FA384
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Weekly Briefing Notes for the President and Vice President and STATUS: A Monthly Chartbook of Social and Economic Trends, 1975-1977 (Box 46, Volume 46)
  Weekly Briefing Notes STATUS: Presidential Authorization (July 16, 1975). VP Meeting with Federal Interagency Committee (September 23, 1975). July-December 1975. January 1-April 20, 1976. Review Meeting (April 21, 1976). Prototype (May 1976). Office of Management and Budget (OMB) Social Indicators Advisory Committee Meeting (May 20, 1976). May 21-June 30, 1976. July 1976. August 1976. September 1976. October 1976. November 1976. January 1977.
- Weekly STATUS Reports to the Vice President, 1975 July 25-December 12 (Box 47, Volume 47)
- Weekly STATUS Reports to the Vice President, 1976 January-June (Box 48, Volume 48)
- Weekly STATUS Reports to the Vice President, 1976 July-1977 January (Box 49, Volume 49)
- Press Book (I), 1974 September-December (Box 50, Volume 50)
  Chronological collection of statements, speeches, press releases and press conference transcripts:
  NAR Statement at beginning of Senate Confirmation Hearings, September 23, 1974. Speech, Brigham Young University, October 2, 1974. Speech, UPI Editors & Publishers, San Francisco, California, October 2, 1974. Press Advisory, re: More Tax Information, October 8, 1974. Press Questions, on Departure for Warrenton, VA, October 8, 1974. Statement, Laurance S. Rockefeller, October 10, 1974. NAR Interview, October 11, 1974. Telegram to Congressman Edward Mezvinsky, re: Release of Gifts and Loans, October 11, 1974. Letter to Chairman Howard Cannon, re: Gifts to Public Officials and Others, October 11, 1974. Statement, re: Lasky Book and Telegram to Goldberg, October 1974. Statement by Hugh Morrow, re: Delay in Hearings, October 15, 1974. NAR Interview, October 15, 1974. Statement, re: Delay in Hearings, October 15, 1974. Statement, re: Delay in Hearings, October 16, 1974. NAR Interview for German TV, October 16, 1974. Press Conference, October 16, 1974. Press Conference, October 17, 1974. Letter to Chairman Cannon, re: Summary of Taxes, October 18, 1974. NAR Response to Questions: Taxes, October 20, 1974. Letter to Chairman Cannon, re: Summary of Gifts, October 20, 1974. Press Questions to NAR, entering hospital, October 21, 1974. NAR Sidewalk Interview, October 22, 1974. Statement re: Deferring Answering Questions, October 22, 1974. Press Advisory, re: NAR Attendance at White House Dinner for Gen. and Mrs. Haig, Oct. 23, 1974. Press Advisory, re: Mrs. NAR Departure from hospital, October 23, 1974. Letters to Chairman Cannon and [Peter] Rodino, re: Lists of Loans from 1952-1974, Oct. 28, 1974. Statement by Hugh Morrow, re: "New York Post" story, November 1, 1974. Statement to "New York Times," November 8, 1974. Statement before Senate Rules Committee, November 13, 1974. Statement by Laurance S. Rockefeller before Senate Rules Committee, November 14, 1974. Press Questions on arrival at Page National Airport, November 21, 1974. Statement before House Judiciary Committee, November 21, 1974. Press Questions to NAR at hospital upon Mrs. NAR arrival, November 24, 1974. Statement to amplify responses to Questions of Rep. Eilberg, November 30, 1974. Statement by J. Richardson Dilworth before House Judiciary Committee, December 3, 1974. Statement by Laurance S. Rockefeller before House Judiciary Committee, December 14, 1974. Transcript of Phone Call to NAR upon Senate Confirmation, December 10, 1974. Press Conference following Senate Confirmation, December 10, 1974. Press Questions to NAR following Phone Conversation with Rep. McClory, December 12, 1974. Remarks by Foreign Minister Allon, December 12, 1974. Speech, Inauguration Ceremony, December 19, 1974.
- Press Book (II), 1975 January-April (Box 51, Volume 51)
  Luncheon/Toast to Sultan of Oman, Press Release, January 10, 1975. Statement at First Meeting of CIA Commission, January 13, 1975. Statement on State of Union Message, January 15, 1975. NAR Remarks at President Ford's Briefing of Governors and Mayors, January 16, 1975. NAR Announcement of Sol Corbin for CIA Commission, January 16, 1975. Congratulations from Senator [Mike] Mansfield on record attendance in Senate, January 17, 1975. Press Briefing, CIA Commission, January 20, 1975. Speech, Outstanding Driver of the Year Award, January 21, 1975. NAR Remarks at Swearing-in of Nuclear Regulatory Commission, January 23, 1975. NAR Remarks, Press Release, National Business Leadership Conference - Chicago, Illinois, January 23, 1975. Statement, Swearing-in of Marjorie Lynch to Bicentennial Administration, January 24, 1975. Speech, World Wildlife Fund Getty Prize for Conservation, January 23, 1975. Speech, NJ Republican Finance Committee Dinner, Milburn, NJ, January 29, 1975. NAR Remarks following CIA Commission meeting, February 3, 1975. Speech, 2nd Annual US Tourism State Days Conference, February 4, 1975. Press Briefing with New York Governor Hugh Carey and New York City Mayor Abe Beame, February 6, 1975. NAR Remarks following CIA Commission Meeting, February 10, 1975. Announcement of Professional Staff Appointments of CIA Commission (incl. biographies), February 13, 1975. Speech, "Salute to VP Dinner," Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, NYC, February 13, 1975. NAR Remarks following CIA Commission Meeting, February 17, 1975. Speech, National Governors' conference, Mayflower Hotel, Washington, DC, February 19, 1975. Speech, National Affairs Conference Chamber of Commerce, Washington Hilton, Washington, DC, February 19, 1975. Speech, Press Release, Society of Automotive Engineers, Detroit, Michigan, February 26, 1975. Statement, Critical Choices, New York, February 28, 1975. Speech, Republican National Committee Leadership Luncheon, Washington Hilton, Washington, DC, March 7, 1975. CIA Commission Meeting, March 10, 1975. Statement on appointment of Thad Garrett, March 19, 1975. Letter from Andrew Stein, Chairman of Commission on Living Costs, March 19, 1975. Speech, Coal Conference, the White House, March 21, 1975. Speech, Gridiron Club, March 22, 1975. Q&A following CIA Commission Meeting, March 24, 1975. Briefing to Federal Employees, March 25, 1975. Press Conference aboard Air Force II, returning from Saudi Arabia, March 28, 1975. NAR Remarks following CIA Commission Meeting, March 31, 1975. Q&A at Department of Transportation, April 2, 1975. Speech, Award Ceremony for Handicapped Federal Employees, April 2, 1975. Speech, Department of Commerce, April 3, 1975. NAR Remarks at Swearing-in of Henry Smith as Chairman, U.S. and Canada Joint Commission, April 7, 1975 NAR Remarks following CIA Commission Meeting, April 7, 1975. Press Conference on arrival, New Orleans, Louisiana, April 9, 1975. Speech, American Newspaper Publishers Association, April 9, 1975. Statement on Stanley Hathaway Nomination for Secretary of Interior, April 9, 1975. Press Conference aboard Air Force II, returning from New Orleans, April 9, 1975. Speech, President's Commission on Personnel Interchange, Washington, DC, April 10, 1975. NAR Remarks to National Association of Manufacturers, Washington Hilton, Washington, DC, April 11, 1975. Statement on Purchase of Texas Land, April 11, 1975. Statement on Appointment of John Veneman as Counselor, April 14, 1975. Press Conference, en route to Taipei, April 14, 1975. NAR Remarks and Q&A, Young Presidents Organization, Boca Raton, Florida, April 18, 1975. Statement on Death of Frank Little, April 20, 1975. NAR Remarks Following CIA Commission Meeting, April 21, 1975. NAR Remarks, Advertising Council, Washington, DC, April 23, 1975. NAR Remarks, Marconi Awards, National Academy of Engineering, Washington, DC, April 23, 1975. NAR Remarks, Library of Congress 175th Opening, April 21, 1975. NAR Remarks, National Volunteer Awards Ceremony, April 24, 1975. Speech, Annual Spring Reception New York Senate Campaign Committee, Lincoln Center, NYC, April 27, 1975. NAR Remarks, U.S. Chamber of Commerce International General Session, Washington, DC, April 29,1975. Press Conference, U.S. Chamber of Commerce International General Session, Washington, DC, April 29, 1975. Speech, Annual Convention of Garden Clubs of America, Washington, DC, April 29, 1975. Press Conference, Annual Convention of Garden Clubs of America, Washington, DC, April 29, 1975.
- Press Book (III), 1975 May-September 11 (Box 52, Volume 52)
  Remarks, National Urban Coalition, May 1, 1975. Statement on Appointment of Governor Raymond P. Shafer as Counselor, May 1, 1975. Statement on Death of Kenneth Keating, May 1, 1975. Statement, Institutional Investors Institute, Washington, DC (noted as "Off the Record"), May 6, 1975. Speech, Business Council, Hot Springs, Virginia, May 9, 1975. Press Conference, Hot Springs, Virginia, May 9, 1975. Remarks, and Q&A, National Republican Heritage Group Council, May 16, 1975. Press Conference, May 16, 1975. Remarks, Black Caucus Forum on Employment, May 20, 1975. Speech, Awards Ceremony for the Blind, May 21, 1975. Remarks and Q&A, Bull Elephants, May 21, 1975. Remarks Following CIA Commission Meeting, June 2, 1975. Remarks, US Naval Academy, Annapolis, Maryland, June 4, 1975. Statement on Senator Kennedy on White House Science Advisory Conference, June 4, 1975. Statement on CIA Involvement in Assassinations, June 5, 1975. Speech, White House Science Advisory Conference, June 6, 1975. Remarks, Delta Sigma Chi, June 6, 1975. Remarks, House Science Technology Committee, June 10, 1975. Speech, NYS Republican Committee, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, NYC, June 12, 1975. Interview with Connie Chung aboard Air Force II, June 15, 1975. Statement on Ann Whitman's Return to New York, June 24, 1975. Statement on Appointment of Quincy Rodgers to Privacy Commission, June 26, 1975. Speech, National Commission on Water Quality, Atlanta, Georgia, July 9, 1975. Speech, Conference of Mayors, July 10, 1975. Joint Cabinet Briefing, July 10, 1975. Remarks at Awards Ceremony for Colonel Jack Walker, July 14, 1975. Remarks, Q&A, Midwestern Conference, July 22, 1975. Press Conference at Netherlands Hilton Hotel, Cincinnati, Ohio, July 22, 1975. Press Release, re: appointment of R. Heath Larry as Counsel to Vice President, July 31, 1975. Remarks to White House Summer Interns, August 5, 1975. Press Release, re: Hospital Productivity Center, Austin, Texas, August 6, 1975. Press Release, re: Admiral's House Parties, August 11, 1975. Remarks at Dinner of Lieutenant Governors Conference, Mobile, Alabama, August 26, 1975. Remarks, Press Conference, Lace House, Columbia, South Carolina, August 27, 1975. Remarks, GOP Reception, Columbia, South Carolina, August 27, 1975. Transcript, TV Appearance with Ed Rowland, Fred McNeese, Jan Stucker, Columbia, South Carolina, August 27, 1975. Press Conference, Columbia, South Carolina, August 27, 1975. Press Advisory, re: Housewarming Events at Admiral's House, September 2, 1975. Remarks at J.W. Holler Farm Center, Rochester, NY, September 5, 1975. Remarks at Park Ridge Hospital, Greece, NY, September 5, 1975. Press Conference, Rochester, NY, September 5, 1975. Remarks at Presentation of "Life" magazine Bicentennial Issue, September 11, 1975.
- Press Book (IV), 1975 September 12-October 31 (Box 53, Volume 53)
  Speech, National Federation of Republican Women, Dallas, Texas, September 12, 1975. Press Conference, National Federation of Republican Women, September 12, 1975. Transcript, TV Appearance, Dallas, September 12, 1975. Press Conference, Little Rock, Arkansas, September 12, 1975. Remarks, Little Rock, September 12, 1975. Press Conference, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, September 13, 1975. Remarks, Norman, Oklahoma, September 13, 1975. Remarks, Vance Air Force Base, Enid, Oklahoma, September 13, 1975. Press Conference, Enid, Oklahoma, September 13, 1975. Remarks, Fund-Raising Dinner, Enid, Oklahoma, September 13, 1975. Remarks, British Museum, London, England, September 15, 1975. Remarks, Reading is Fundamental, September 17, 1975. Speech, National Medal of Science, Washington, DC, September 18, 1975. Presentation of "Publick Occurrences," September 24, 1975. Remarks, Federal City Council, September 29, 1975. Speech, Conference on Regional vs. National Interest Energy, October 2, 1975. Press Conference, Hilton Hotel, Portland, Oregon, October 3, 1975. Speech, luncheon for Local Editors and Publishers, Portland, Oregon, October 3, 1975. Speech, Western States Republic Conference Dinner, Portland, October 3, 1975. Speech, Energy Conference, October 2, 1975. Executive Order on Official Seal of Vice President, October 7, 1975. Remarks, Kings Mountain, North Carolina, October 7, 1975. Speech, Roundtable on Privacy and Information Washington, DC, October 8, 1975. Remarks, Launching of Nuclear Power Aircraft Carrier, USS Dwight David Eisenhower, Newport News, Virginia, October 11, 1975. Speech, Columbus Day Dinner, Waldorf-Astoria Hotel, NYC, October 11, 1975. Statement, VIP Reception, Columbus, Ohio, October 15, 1975. Transcript, TV Appearance, WNBS - Columbus, Ohio, October 15, 1975. Press Conference, Columbus, Ohio, October 15, 1975. Speech, GOP Reception, Roanoke, Virginia, October 16, 1975. Press Conference, Roanoke, Virginia, October 16, 1975. Speech, GOP Reception, Charleston, West Virginia, October 16, 1975. Press Conference, Governors House Charleston, West Virginia, October 16, 1975. Speech, Public Forum on Domestic Policy, Denver, Colorado, October 16, 1975. Speech, Macon County Republican Central Committee, Decatur, Illinois, October 23, 1975. Speech, Indiana State Teachers Association, October 23, 1975. Transcript, TV Appearance with John Lindsay, WLWI - Indianapolis, Indiana, October 23, 1975. Speech, Indiana Republican State Committee Luncheon, October 23, 1975. Press Conference, Indianapolis Convention Center, October 23, 1975. Speech, United Negro College Fund Dinner, Pfister Hotel, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, October 24, 1975. Press Conference, Milwaukee, Wisconsin, October 24, 1975. Press Conference, Tampa, Florida, October 28, 1975. Press Conference, Tampa Convention Center, October 29, 1975. Speech, Public Forums on Domestic Council, Tampa, Florida, October 29, 1975. Luncheon Toast to Egyptian President Sadat, Pocantico Hills, October 30, 1975. Speech, Hebrew Union College, October 30, 1975. Introduction of President Sadat, Houston Chamber of Commerce, October 31, 1975.
- Press Book (V), 1975 November-December (Box 54, Volume 54)
  Withdrawal Announcement, November 2, 1975. Address to the Staff, November 5, 1975. Press Conference, re: Withdrawal Announcement, November 6, 1975. Statement, US Chamber of Commerce Board of Directors Meeting, November 6, 1975. Press Conference aboard Air Force II, en route to Austin, November 10, 1975. Speech, Conference on Women in Public Life, LBJ Library, November 10, 1975. Speech, White House Public Forum on Domestic Policy, Austin, Texas, November 11, 1975. Transcript, TV Appearance, Austin Southwest Educational Development Laboratories, November 11, 1975. Speech, Future Farmers of America, Kansas City, November 14, 1975. Transcript, WDAF-TV appearance - Kansas City, Missouri, November 14, 1975. Transcript, WBBM-TV appearance - Lincolnshire, Illinois, November 14, 1975. Speech, McClory Testimonial Dinner, Lincolnshire, Illinois, November 14, 1975. Transcript, KSTP-TV appearance - Minneapolis, Minnesota, November 15, 1975. Remarks and Q&A, Minnesota Metropolitan College Club Luncheon, November 15, 1975. Speech, '76 Spirit Bicentennial Prom Center St. Paul, Minnesota, November 15, 1975. Remarks, Elephant Club Reception Minnesota Club, St. Paul, Minnesota, November 15, 1975. Press Conference, St. Cloud University Campus, St. Cloud, Minnesota, November 15, 1975. Speech, Public Forum on Domestic Policy, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 18, 1975. Press Conference, Benjamin Franklin Hotel, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 18, 1975. Speech, Council of 100 Dinner, Washington, DC, November 18, 1975. Press Conference, McConnell Air Force Base, Wichita, Kansas, November 20, 1975. Speech, Kansas State GOP Reception, Wichita, Kansas, November 20, 1975. Remarks, Speech, Republican Governors' Conference, Wichita, Kansas, November 21, 1975. Statement, Moreland Commission on Urban Development Commission, December 3, 1975. Press Conference, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, December 4, 1975. Speech, Republican Awards Dinner, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, December 4, 1975. Speech, National Association of Manufacturers Luncheon, NYC, December 5, 1975. Speech, Public Forum on Domestic Policy, Los Angeles, California, December 9, 1975. Press Conference, Los Angeles, December 9, 1975. Transcript, KNBC-TV Appearance, Los Angeles, California, December 9, 1975. Statement, Council on Environmental Quality, Washington, DC, December 10, 1975. Press Conference, Metro Center, Nashville, Tennessee, December 11, 1975. Speech, Republican State Committee Luncheon, Nashville, Tennessee, December 11, 1975. Speech, Black Republican Leadership Conference, Houston, Texas, December 11, 1975. Speech, Houston Business & Professional Mens Club Dinner, Houston, Texas, December 11, 1975. Speech, Southern Republican Conference, Houston, Texas, December 12, 1975. Press Conference, Houston, Texas, December 12, 1975. Transcript, KTRK-TV Appearance - Houston, Texas, December 12, 1975. Press Conference on Domestic Council Forums, December 17, 1975. Statement, President's Safety Awards for 1974, December 17, 1975.
- Press Book (VI), 1976 January-April 12 (Box 55, Volume 55)
  Speech, National Council of Farmer Cooperatives, January 14, 1976. Statement, National Commission on Water Quality Hearing, January 19, 1976. Speech, Opening of the Second Session of the 94th Congress, January 19, 1976. Statement on Conclusion of Public Hearings on National Commission on Water Quality, January 20, 1976. Speech, Salem College Convocation, Salem, West Virginia, January 26, 1976. Speech, Westchester County Republican Dinner, January 29, 1976. Press Conference with Midwest Republican Leaders, Dearborn, Michigan, January 30, 1976. Speech, GOP Reception, Dearborn, Michigan, January 30, 1976. Press Conference, re: Revenue Sharing Briefing the White House, February 3, 1976. Letter to the President (dated December 16, 1975), re: End of Responsibilities at Domestic Council, February 4, 1976. Testimony, Senate Committee on Government Operations, February 4, 1976. Speech, National Council on the Arts, February 6, 1976. Speech, Northeast Republican Leadership Luncheon, Washington, DC, February 7, 1976. Introduction of President Ford, February 6, 1976. Speech, Atomic Industrial Forum Conference Luncheon, Washington, DC, February 10, 1976. Press Conference, Louisville, Kentucky, February 12, 1976. Speech, Kentucky State GOP Central Committee Meeting, Louisville, Kentucky, February 12, 1976. Transcript, WAVE-TV appearance, Louisville, Kentucky, February 12, 1976. Speech, GOP Lincoln Day Dinner, February 12, 1976. Speech, New York Republic County Dinner, February 14, 1976. Speech, National Press Club, February 19, 1976. Press Conference, Holiday Inn, Lansing, Michigan, February 20, 1976. Speech, Michigan State Republican Committee Dinner, Lansing, Michigan, February 20, 1976. Speech, American Association for the Advancement of Science, Boston, Massachusetts, February 23, 1976. Speech, National Governors Conference, Washington, DC, February 24, 1976. Remarks at Swearing-in of Arthur Fletcher, February 25, 1976. Speech, Bicentennial Bishops and Conventional Church Council Banquet, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, February 26, 1976. "Newsday" Interview, March 4, 1976. Interview with Martin Diamond, March 4, 1976. Remarks, Religion in American Life, March 9, 1976. Press Conference, Albuquerque, New Mexico, March 12, 1976. Speech, Lincoln Day Dinner, Albuquerque, New Mexico, March 12, 1976. Speech, National American Wholesale Grocers Association, Chicago, Illinois, March 16, 1976. Press Conference, Chicago, Illinois, March 17, 1976. Statement, Economic Freedom in Bicentennial America, March 17, 1976. Statement, Joint Economic Committee, March 18, 1976. Press Release, National Water Quality Commission Report, March 18, 1976. Statement, Right of Privacy, March 19, 1976. Bicentennial Address, Paris, France, March 22, 1976. Toast at State Banquet, Singapore, March 28, 1976. Remarks, American Business Leaders Reception, Singapore, March 28, 1976. Press Conference, Canberra, Australia, March 30, 1976. Speech, Bicentennial Testimonial Banquet, Sydney, Australia, March 31, 1976. Speech, New Zealand State Luncheon, April 2, 1976. Press Conference, Wellington, New Zealand, April 2, 1976. Speech, National Energy Leadership Conference, Reston, Virginia, April 7, 1976. Transcript, WETA-TV appearance - Arlington, Virginia, April 8, 1976. Testimony to create Energy Independence Authority, April 12, 1976.
- Press Book (VII), 1976 April 12-June 30 (Box 56, Volume 56)
  Remarks, President Ford Committee Reception - Urban Club, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, April 12, 1976. Speech, Club of Rome Banquet, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, April 12, 1976. Press Conference, Des Moines, Iowa, April 14, 1976. Press Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, April 18, 1976. Speech, GOP Fund Raising Reception, Atlanta, Georgia, April 15, 1976. Transcript, WHO-TV appearance - Des Moines, Iowa, April 15, 1976. "60 Minutes" interview, April 18, 1976. Remarks, President's Commission on Personnel Interchange Dinner, April 20, 1976. Telegram exchange with Senator Jackson, April 22, 1976. Speech, Annual Neptune Award Dinner, Washington, DC, April 28, 1976. Statement, Proposals for a National Health Policy, Washington, DC, April 29, 1976. Remarks, George Washington Inaugural Ceremony, Washington Monument, April 30, 1976. Transcript, "Issues and Answers," May 2, 1976. Press Conference, San Francisco, California, May 4, 1976. Speech, Commonwealth Club of California Luncheon - San Francisco, California, May 4, 1976. Press Conference, Los Angeles, California, May 5, 1976. Speech, Los Angeles World Affairs Council Luncheon, May 5, 1976. Speech, Queens County Annual Republican Dinner, Astoria, NY, May 7, 1976. Speech, International Press Institute, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, May 10, 1976. Interview with Ard (German Television Network), May 10, 1976. Remarks upon arrival at Udine, Italy, May 13, 1976. Remarks upon departure from Udine, Italy, May 13, 1976. Remarks upon arrival at Berlin, Germany, May 13, 1976. Speech, U.S. Mission Headquarters, Berlin, Germany, May 14, 1976. Speech, Schloss Charlottenburg Luncheon, Berlin, May 14, 1976. Remarks upon departure from Berlin, Germany, May 14, 1976. Remarks upon arrival at Frankfurt, Germany, May 14, 1976. Speech, Frankfurt City Hall, Germany May 14, 1976. Statement, Opening of Glass Exhibition, Frankfurt, Germany, May 15, 1976. Remarks, Frankfurt, Germany, May 15, 1976. Remarks upon departure from Frankfurt, Germany, May 15, 1976. Remarks between the President, Vice President, and Daniel Parker, aide, May 17, 1976. Speech, Bicentennial Ceremony, Yorktown, Virginia, May 19, 1976. Remarks, Hamilton County President Ford Committee Dinner, Cincinnati, Ohio, May 20, 1976. Speech, Fifteenth Anniversary Synagogue Council of America, Newport, Rhode Island, May 23, 1976. Speech, National Conference on Regulatory Reform, May 26, 1976. Transcript, "Face the Nation," May 30, 1976. Speech, USAF Commencement, Colorado Springs, Colorado, June 2, 1976. Press Conference, USAF Academy, Colorado Springs, June 2, 1976. Remarks on Ronald Reagan, June 3, 1976. Speech, Maryland State Republican Convention Dinner, Ocean City, Maryland, June 4, 1976. Press Conference, June 4, 1976. Speech, National Broadcast Editorial Association Annual Meeting, June 9, 1976. Remarks, Dedication of Old Senate Chamber, June 16, 1976. Speech, National Housing Conference Dinner, June 16, 1976. Remarks, NYS Republican Committee Meeting, NYC, June 17, 1976. Speech, NYS Republican State Dinner, NYC, June 17, 1976. Press Conference, Greensboro, North Carolina, June 18, 1976. Speech, North Carolina Republican State Dinner, Greensboro, June 18, 1976. Remarks, GOP Reception, Greensboro, June 18, 1976. Press Conference, West Orange, New Jersey, June 21, 1976. Remarks, NJ Republican Pre-Convention Dinner, West Orange, New Jersey, June 21, 1976. Speech, American Friends of Hebrew University Luncheon, Washington, DC, June 22, 1976. Press Conference, Hauppauge, NY, June 24, 1976. Speech, Nassau County Republican Committee Dinner, Hauppauge, NY, June 24, 1976. Remarks, Congressman Paul Findley Award Luncheon, June 30, 1976.